Welcome back once again.
I'm in Chants of Sinar.
It's been a couple days since I played last, but I did unlock everything in this language.
Check that out.
Isn't that beautiful?
Part of me wants to just sort of walk around and listen to all the conversations now that I know all the glyphs.
Greetings!
A warrior you're not.
Ascented do you want.
That's such a weird sentence though.
Who says that?
Ascent you don't.
The path you won't find.
Except I found it already!
To ascend we don't want.
Beauty we found.
Idiot ascending is... What?
That doesn't make any sense.
This should have been stupid.
Unless they're talking about the actual idiot who is ascending.
I thought she was about to say...
It's stupid to ascend.
You know?
Don't ascend.
It's dumb.
Whatever.
I'm not going to listen to them.
I'm going to ascend, dammit.
Now we also have a different mystery altogether.
Which is all those zoom calls at the fast travel locations.
I'm not quite sure what's going on with those.
We gotta go back and check that out.
Kind of want to go back to the very beginning.
I actually forgot where these things are.
In this level.
Ah, here's the deal.
We're going to try and ascend now.
Since we have the device.
We put it in the receptacle.
And we can ascend now like an idiot.
I can't wait to see what the next area is going to be like.
Oh, here it is.
This way.
Way up.
I think so far this has been my favorite area.
Just the aesthetics of it.
Ah, but then again the first area was super nice as well.
I don't know.
It's close.
Tied between the third and the first for me so far.
Let's go.
Lovely colors.
Oh no.
The idiot carries the saw.
Can't do anything with that.
Let's try going this way.
Oh, that's where I came from.
Right.
Except it wasn't.
I went this way just now.
What?
Okay, let's try going up here.
Huh?
Wait a minute.
Now I came from here.
Wait, what the?
Something's going on here.
What about this way?
You gotta be kidding me.
Okay, what about down here?
Hmm.
Back out.
What?
Hmm, wait a sec, wait a sec.
I'm being reminded of the plane now.
Didn't that guy go north, south, east, west or something?
Let me see what it said.
The idiot bard, that's me now.
To ascend the idiot bard sought.
The path the idiot bard sought, yes.
The saw he found, west he went.
Okay, and we know this way is north, right?
And then the instrument he found, and he...
Okay, okay, okay, I think I know exactly what to do here.
It's a little bit funky, but I think I need to do it in the right order.
So now I found the saw, I know this is north.
At least, is it?
No, that's north!
Okay, never mind.
That doesn't make too much sense, though, with the layout of the previous level.
But okay, okay, whatever.
Um, whatever.
So the way I came from is north, that means this is west, technically.
Which is funny.
Actually, I should be doing this.
Yeah, yeah, this is west.
So if that is west, I gotta go this way first, right?
Let's see.
The saw he found, west he went.
Okay.
I'm reenacting the play!
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, musical instrument.
The instrument he found, he went north.
Has it changed?
Ooh, it has changed!
Those sneaky fuckers.
Okay, he went this way now.
Okay, now we have the fire.
The fire he found, then he went east.
Okay, so it's this way now.
Beautiful, and the compass.
And then he went south, which is which way?
This way.
Haha, this is pretty cool.
What a great puzzle.
And the sword, then he went west.
Okay.
It's this way.
Nice!
And then we found a bone.
Uh-oh.
Why does it look like a big beast broke out of there?
That's not very reassuring.
Ooh!
Minecarts!
They were trying to mine Cenar?
Oh, I'm loving this angle.
Oh!
Fuck me!
I was not expecting to get scared in this game.
That one got me.
Oh, I think I know where I'm going.
I'm going to the domain of the impure.
Oh, shit.
The monsters!
Can't go that way.
Wait, this is like a prison.
Wait, not really.
These are just mine tracks.
Railways.
Can't interact with that either.
Okay, just go!
Okay, that's a monster!
What?
What's happening?
Do I...
What?
Fuck!
I thought he was like, come with me.
You know, he was beckoning me.
I trusted him.
Last time I'm doing that.
Yeah, this time we're just leaving.
I thought it was like, hey, come here.
Follow me.
Okay, I'm going.
Kind of want to go back.
Oh.
I'm going down here.
Wait, is his vision based on...
Well, not movement, I guess, because he would come for me.
Whoa, wait a minute.
Can he only see me in the darkness?
Wait a sec.
I think that's what it is.
Or not that.
Maybe he's afraid of the light.
If I stay in the light, we're going to be fine.
Oh my God, this is not what I expected.
Oh, it's time to sneak.
We've got multiple levers over there.
Oh shit, oh shit.
Okay, where are you going next?
Maybe we go now?
Shit!
Pull it up!
Oh, God damn it.
Okay.
Now he's looking that way.
Now he's looking that way, okay.
I need to see what he's doing.
As he walks over there, he's going to look this way.
Yeah.
I'm not sure where to go even.
Maybe I go over here.
Maybe I don't want to pull this lever.
Then he walks over here.
Okay, maybe I have to go this way first.
Go.
Don't see me now.
Ooh, that was close.
I think it may be randomized as well, in which direction he's going.
It's not always the same.
Okay.
Go.
Then over here.
Walk over here, please.
Okay, we have to wait.
Where are the warriors when you need them?
Uh oh, bad idea, bad idea.
No, we're fine, we're fine, we're fine.
We can probably go now.
Oh shit!
Leave!
Oh, are we good?
Okay, so that leads back.
Oh shit!
I'm sorry, sorry.
Back in.
Then he comes back in here.
Oh!
When would I be able to go over there?
Oh, maybe if I go along here and then do that one.
Yeah, I can hide here too.
I think I get it.
Go, go, go.
Quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick.
Fast, fast, fast, fast, fast.
Ooh, hoo hoo.
I did not expect this sort of thing.
Oh shit, don't see me.
We don't go yet, we don't go yet.
We have to look the other way.
Maybe that works...
Go!
Quick!
Light!
No, no, it didn't save.
Okay, okay.
So that's going to release light over here.
That's good, that's good.
That's the way to do it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh.
What's happening?
Are we good?
We're not good.
I gotta leave.
Back in.
Holy shit.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
I'm terrible at this.
So we gotta get over here first, release this thing, pull it up, so we can walk over here later.
Oh no, oh no.
Okay, go, go, go, go, go, go.
That's good, that's good.
Go now, go now, go now.
Wonderful.
Now when is the best time to pull this lever?
Would be now, right?
Except he sees me when he walks over here and turns that way again.
So perhaps I do it at a different time.
When he's over here, he looks... okay, that could work maybe.
Maybe.
And he walks back this way.
I think we start by going to this spot.
Go.
Oh god.
I thought maybe he's gonna see me.
This is not very tall.
Don't see me.
Get ready.
And we do it now.
Go.
Quick.
I don't know what to do.
Oh, what's this?
Oh.
Oh shit, I didn't even realize I could do that.
Uh, can I... what can I do with that?
What is that?
What do I hit?
Oh.
Go.
Quick.
Run to the light!
Okay.
Fucking hell.
This is scary as fuck.
Okay, go in.
Go in.
My god.
This is gonna open, isn't it?
Something's gonna happen.
Monster incoming.
Shit!
What the fuck?
Close it!
Brother!
Okay.
Oh my god.
Go, go, go, go, go.
What the fuck outta here?
Okay.
Uh, multiple directions?
What's this?
Oh god, new language!
Wait, that guy looks like the, uh, the detective.
The dude from the zoom call.
Oh, these look interesting.
Circle triangle, half moon, line, double line.
What?
This could mean on.
Okay.
Huh?
So this is for an elevator?
Let's try going this way first.
I'm gonna be back later.
Oh!
Look at that.
And look at this!
Hold on, let me, let me look at this here again.
You know what?
I'm getting overwhelmed already.
Maybe I want to go back to the very first area now and try and figure out what the hell is going on with this thing.
Let's go to... Also, why are there circles on some of these?
There's no circles on this, this one or that one.
Let's go to the first one.
I think that was the first one at least.
Oh, so bright yellow.
Nice.
Okay, let's see here.
So what are these dots supposed to represent?
There's five dots, and they're all sort of swirling around.
And then the TIE fighter.
Wait, what?
You help me.
Plants are dying.
I don't understand what's...
Wait, what?
Oh, wait, we have things over here.
I don't want plants to die.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I see!
No, no, no.
Erase.
Okay, okay.
Wait a minute.
How do I switch this language over here?
So the detective is talking to the devotee.
Okay.
Wait, let me check that one.
I gotta take a look at that one.
Okay, let's see this one.
So here, okay, so there's nothing here.
There's no connection here.
The devotee is trying to contact somebody, but the connection is not there.
And that's why there's no circle on it, I think.
All right, okay.
That makes sense, I guess.
Go back here.
So now when I go in here...
I... How do I get the alphabet of the others over here?
So I can plop things into this one.
I don't understand.
Do I...
click on these or...
Why is this so confusing?
Stop opening the book!
Just go to the next line.
Unless you have to do it in this order.
Hold on a minute.
Let's try going to one of the others.
Let's try that one.
Oh, I'm still wearing the disguise here.
That's funny.
Okay, now there's still five dots.
Okay, so look at this here.
Yo, what is this language?
So the detective is talking to the warrior...
saying something.
And here I'm supposed to fill in...
uh, well, warrior language.
Which makes sense, I guess, because this is linked to the detective.
Right?
This is all him.
Then on the other side, we have the warriors, which is what he's saying.
Is he just trying to translate the sentence directly?
Let's go this one.
I'm grateful that I finally sort of understand a little bit more here.
The fact that you can click on these symbols on the right.
Okay, so...
The impure ones do not pass.
Right, and it's, uh, plural.
Right, so let's... let's just look at this again.
Do we have words for, uh, impure ones here?
I forgot if we did.
This is the devotee language, by the way.
Which makes sense, because, uh, the warrior is talking to the devotee.
Not.
So in which order do we do this?
So we start with the impure ones.
So first we need plural.
Plural was, um, what was plural?
I forgot.
Was that one?
No.
Love like...
Let's see.
We need that one.
Death dead.
Not.
We need that one.
I cannot find it.
Music.
Garden.
Oh, plural was just two of the same thing.
That's right.
I remember now.
So what we need is impure ones, and what do they call those?
Oh god.
I'm having great difficulty finding this glyph.
What did the devotees call the impure ones?
God.
Are you kidding me?
I can't find it.
God, warrior.
Uh...
I feel like I'm losing my mind.
Am I blind?
Maybe they consider them death?
I don't know.
Okay, so hold on.
Every type of person has this sort of L, right?
devotees, men, preacher, all of that.
So I guess we look for those.
Preacher.
And that's pretty much it here.
Me.
Dude, I don't know.
The impure ones do not create music.
So they are hating on the impure ones because they don't do music.
They love the chosen ones because of the music, right?
We know that.
I don't understand.
What is that word for impure one?
What was the saying?
Protect against something?
Ah, but we never got that, did we?
That was in the warrior domain.
Did we ever learn anything about the impure ones from this floor?
I don't think we did.
So we don't know what the word is for that.
The lens found God.
What could be the equivalent of impure ones at this floor?
Maybe God?
Preacher?
No, none of that makes sense.
Ah, man.
So we need four glyphs here.
Impure ones, that's plural, so we need two of them.
Not pass.
Right?
So something, something, not pass.
Which makes sense.
Did we get a recetta stone in the warrior domain?
For this sort of thing?
Love, warrior, death.
Not.
Pushes back the impure.
Right.
Wait a sec.
Wait a minute.
Maybe they consider the devotees impure ones.
No, but we know, no, no, no, we know the monsters exist.
So it can't be that.
We've seen them.
Ah, man, I don't know.
Let's try it, honestly.
Let's try it.
Let's see if I'm right here.
Uh, devotees.
So, what are they?
Maybe it's just men or human.
Is that what they call impure ones?
So we had men, human, preacher.
But we know the monsters exist.
We've seen them.
Warrior.
Preacher.
Let's try this.
Not pass.
Uh, which one was not?
Oh, god, I have to go through all of them now, because I don't remember which one is which.
Not.
Go pass.
Nope.
It's not that one.
Well, fuck.
Let's try the preacher.
I need to see if this is how this works.
Maybe the preacher is the impure one in this language, even though that doesn't make any sense.
Not pass.
Not that one either.
At least I'm making progress here.
Could it be god?
Not pass.
Nope.
So if the warriors do consider the devotees impure ones, right now he's speaking directly to them, right?
So he would be saying you.
You do not pass.
Right?
That's what they're doing.
They're actually holding the devotees back.
They're guarding the gate.
You.
Not.
Pass.
Nah, that's it.
I'm done.
I give up.
I don't want to try and brute force this shit.
I don't understand it.
I don't get it.
We saw the impure ones.
We've been chased by them.
We know they exist.
They gotta have a word for it.
Something like god, right?
Because they consider god on high.
He's up there in the sky.
Who else do we know is up high?
The monsters, right?
They're in the top floors.
I don't get it.
Okay, so these guys are now speaking to the devotees.
Saying something.
And the response is, I salute the man.
So I guess this guy is saying greetings.
Do we have a word for man here?
I don't think we had a word for man specifically.
We have monster.
We have a bard.
Then we had... what else?
Oh, just look for the ones where it goes through the bottom.
Like this one.
Man human.
There it is.
I salute the man.
So...
me?
We need a me.
Greetings.
Greetings was that one.
The man.
You gotta be kidding me.
Ah, but wait, these guys speak differently, right?
So we have to rearrange it.
So in this case, it would be the man I salute.
Man.
I salute.
So me.
Greetings.
Oh, where was it?
Where was it?
God damn it.
Greetings.
That one.
There we go!
Finally!
Okay, so it is a direct translation.
Good.
Men, we are not.
In this case, it would be we are not men.
So we, right, so two times me.
I guess.
So let's look for me.
Two times me.
Uh, are.
But wait, we don't have a word for that.
Men, we are not.
We... Ah, but wait, I did it in the wrong way.
Fuck.
How do I revert?
Revert!
So now we need to do we are not men.
Oh, yeah, actually, that was fine.
That was fine the way it is.
Yeah, we.
Yeah, that was fine.
We are, but we don't have a word for orange language, I don't think.
But I guess we have a knot.
And we have men.
Right.
We...
Are.
Do we have an are?
To be?
Or not to be?
No.
We don't have a thing like that.
Maybe we have to find the closest thing to it.
We are not men.
How else could you say it?
Maybe you do three me to go we and when you go to me, you go us.
I don't know.
Ah, man.
Let's try three.
Not men.
Nah.
Shit.
We are not men.
It's like I'm missing certain glyphs outside of what I've already found, you know?
I don't know what their word is for are.
In this case.
You know, to be.
They don't have anything close to it either.
Ah, but wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
We are not men.
It's plural.
That's where the extra one comes in.
I see now.
Right.
So we...
Whoops.
Fuck wrong.
Back.
We.
Uh, shit.
Why do I have such trouble finding these things?
There we go.
We are not men.
Yes.
Fantastic.
Okay.
Free, we are not.
We are not free.
That was the glyph I had so much trouble getting in the first area.
The one with the bird.
There we go.
I salute the men.
We are not men.
We are not free.
The abbey is free.
Come to us.
Yeah, exactly.
Come to abbey.
Dude, this is awesome.
Okay, okay, abbey is free.
Uh, so here we have to go...
Here we have to write, free, the abbey is, I guess.
Or maybe abbey free is.
I'm not sure.
Free, abbey is.
Yeah.
We gotta look for free.
Free, abbey.
And abbey was one of those with the dots on it.
That was a place.
Theater, windmill, abbey.
Abbey to be.
Nice.
Come to abbey.
Okay.
Abbey, come to, in this case.
So we start with abbey.
Um...
Ah, but wait a minute.
Come to ab... Why are there four here now?
Come to abbey... abbey?
Come to... Do we have a word for a come?
Maybe, uh...
Path?
Come to abbey.
I think this one may be it, but...
Let's just see here.
Free, book, east.
Okay.
It's gotta be path.
So how would that work?
So we say abbey...
Path to...
We got multiple words missing here.
Come to abbey.
Why is this, uh...
Plural.
Is the abbey a plural?
Plural?
Wait, I don't understand this.
Also, no, this right here is...
What is that even?
Is that you?
Let's see here.
It is!
Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Why is the translation come to abbey when it clearly says...
You...
Come to abbey.
Also, what is that symbol right there?
Um, let's take a look.
Go path, of course, of course.
Yeah.
You go abbey.
Well, why is it translated come to abbey?
The translation is confusing me.
I should look at the glyphs and not the translation, because the translation is weird.
Okay, so here we need to do a plural.
So we gotta throw in this guy.
Oh, no, he's saying you guys, right?
So actually, yeah, wrong, wrong, wrong.
So abbey, we know that one.
And then he's saying you guys, so in plural, all of you.
So that would be this one, followed by that one.
Go.
And go pass is that one.
Beautiful!
Oh!
Something has changed in the tower!
I think I know what happened.
Did we open one of those doors we couldn't access earlier?
We are creating connections between the civilizations, the cultures.
Oh my god.
He's accepting.
Yes, I'm coming over there.
Oh!
That's awesome!
Oh, and the circle is filled!
That's wonderful.
Okay, back to this one.
We gotta be able to do it, right?
Let's see now.
Okay, so here we apparently have to use this language first, which we can't do right now.
Because we gotta get the language first.
I don't know what these mean, right?
So we can't actually do this one just yet.
And this one...
I'll be able to do that one yet.
Let's take a look.
We cannot do this one either because the language this guy speaks, the detective, is a language we haven't learned yet.
So this one is also undoable at the moment.
Oh, why do I keep going out?
I don't want to do that.
Sorry.
Back in.
Take me to this guy now.
I'm checking them one by one.
I want to see how many I can do right now.
Okay, here?
Okay, this one we should be able to do.
The impure ones do not pass.
But there is no word for impure ones.
Okay, let's look at the words.
I mean glyphs.
So this one is clearly impure ones.
He must be considering these guys as impure ones.
Look, he's, he's begging.
He's pleading.
Come on, please.
And he's like, no, you cannot pass.
Hold on, am I being hoodwinked here?
Am I being falsely led to believe that the monsters that I literally saw at the top of the tower are not actually what the soldiers consider impure?
But in that case, what would the soldiers consider impure?
What are their values?
Okay, so the impure ones do not pass.
So we need...
to double up on the thing we need to pluralize.
We know that.
And I think I tried these already, right?
I tried you, not pass, didn't work.
Yeah, it's wrong.
So...
So what?
Preacher didn't work.
Me.
Remember, it's the warrior speaking right now.
And then we have to do the translation here.
But in the language of the devotee.
Maybe humans?
Does he consider humans trash?
Is that it?
No.
I...
What is the closest thing to a impure or demon here that we have?
Maybe death?
I mean, warriors don't fear death, right?
They don't fear the impure?
Let's try that.
Oh my god.
What about devotee?
I mean, at this point I've exhausted everything else.
God damn it.
Really?
Unbelievable.
I was hoodwinked.
So, the warriors are like...
mega haters on the devotees.
And the chosen ones, or the bards, are mega haters of the warriors.
Everyone's hating each other.
And you know why?
Because there's this disconnect between these cultures.
We gotta bring them together.
And establish peace in the land.
The impure ones do not create music.
Okay.
Let's go impure ones.
Not.
Make.
Music.
Which was...
that one.
It's like, oh, oh no!
We do make music!
So, devotees.
Plural.
Uh...
So, they call them impure ones.
That is nuts.
Uh...
Music.
And I think that looked like...
Yeah, I don't remember the music symbol.
None of those.
Weapon...
Instrument.
Fear.
God damn it.
Where is it?
There.
Nice.
Look!
I can prove it to you!
I play music!
He's impressed!
Warriors love music!
Hell yeah!
Warrior...
Music.
And music was...
Oh, God.
This one.
Look at him!
Yes!
Something has changed in the tower!
Oh, yes!
Let's check out what has changed.
Hey?
Now, I honestly don't remember where I saw this door, but it's gotta be that door, right?
I think I remember where that door was in...
In the first region down here, but we didn't solve anything here yet though, so we gotta stay here.
Now, these ones I can't do yet.
But let's go check out what has changed here.
All right, strap yourselves in for some backtracking.
Hopefully, it's not gonna be too bad with the backtracking.
Right.
I push down this pillar.
I think it's a good idea to just explore from the beginning here, you know?
In case I miss something.
Okay, this looks pretty standard.
Except why are these... Oh!
There's devotees here!
What?!
They let them in because they make music!
Damn, what a plot twist!
Okay.
Uh, take me down there now.
Look at them!
Can I speak to them?
Hey!
Let's head back up here.
By the way, the last time I was here, everything sort of became a little chaotic.
Because I rang the bell and everyone started running.
I wonder where they ran too.
Let's go this way.
Just want to see what else has changed.
Wait, there's nobody here now.
Where did they go?
It's so empty everywhere.
Is that because they all ran towards somewhere?
And they're still there?
So that door's locked.
Uh, go down here.
Yeah, look, everyone's gone.
They all freaking went.
So I got to go back to the bell.
I want to see what's up there.
Uh,
take, uh, let me see.
This one?
Yes.
So weird being back here.
Everyone is gone.
Look.
Oh, where did that elevator go?
I forgot.
Oh, right.
Okay, I don't mind being here.
This is good.
Yeah, take me to the chosen ones.
The area.
What are they doing?
They're all there!
I actually want to check something real fast.
Now that I have the full translation of this place.
Uh...
Hope I can still read that book up there.
Otherwise, I think I have it in my here, don't I?
Warriors?
Uh,
not that one.
I actually don't.
Okay, okay, okay.
Back up here.
The dude has gone up there?
I guess he also went.
What did I actually do when I rang the bell?
Call of the sun.
Call of duty.
Call of the moon.
Call of the chosen ones.
Well, one of these, I guess.
I forgot which one it was.
Let's head back to the bards.
I know where the door is at the bards.
The door that I think requires some kind of key.
But it could be related to...
Um, to the stuff I do at the zoom terminals.
Right?
Because how else do these... Yeah, look, devotees here.
How else would these guys make it here?
If not for...
That door, right?
It's like a back door in a way.
Then again.
Um, if the warriors are now okay with the devotees coming up here, maybe they are no longer guarding the main gate.
Remember from the first area?
Kind of want to check that out.
Let's go back up here though.
Yeah, I think this is my favorite area, just from the looks of it.
Really enjoy the look.
But let me take another look through this place as well.
Now that I know what everyone is saying would be kind of funny to just...
Listen to their conversations again.
I know I'm going pretty slow in this game, but I'm having a good time.
I'm enjoying myself just wandering around.
What is the deal with this contraption anyway?
How exactly does this thing work?
It's attached to this sort of uh...
Well rope, right?
I don't know.
But it looks cool, and that's what matters.
Okay, we know what these guys are saying.
We don't need to ask them.
Did something change in this place?
I think I forgot where the uh... where the teleporter is in this place.
I think I gotta go to the Agora again.
Which is... which direction?
I think up here.
Oh, I remember now.
It's down here to the right.
Over here.
Yeah.
Oh, the people here are gone.
Someone was standing here collecting the piss vassa.
Ah, there we are.
Okay.
This one I believe we can't do either.
Let's see.
No connection.
Okay.
I wonder why that is.
Hmm.
Let's go to the other place here.
No, no, no.
Keep going here actually.
I think I'm in a pretty good spot.
Go further down.
Look, the guy's gone from here now too.
Why?
Maybe they all witnessed my ascent and they were all impressed.
With what was going on there.
Let me go down.
Uh...
Oh no, this is the maze.
I need to remind myself what the other door was.
Oh, the lead's back up here.
Okay.
Yeah, we gotta go this way.
Down here is where I found the door.
So we only have one option now, which is that way.
This leads to up, but where's up?
That's kind of vague.
I have no recollection of where this door is supposed to be.
No clue.
I'll have to try my way again.
There's nothing I can do here.
What a weird room.
Or is there?
Wait.
If I walk to the edge, maybe.
No, I don't see anything here.
This way now.
I don't understand why people are gone from here.
Wait, I can't go through that one.
These are locked.
I can only go this way.
Wasn't this open last time?
Am I crazy?
That one is locked.
This leads to up.
And this one, I don't know.
Let's go that way.
Oh, I like this song so much.
Path to the theater.
What about down here?
Right.
This way.
I like how I'm just pretending to know the way, when I have no idea.
What's down here?
Nothing?
Okay.
Path to the Agora.
So that should lead back to where it came from, right?
But why is it going up then?
There's got to be more.
Okay, I see.
Right.
Last time I went through here, let's go back then.
What a mess.
And I guess we only have one way here.
Now I did not go this way.
Okay, let's go up here.
Way up to theater.
What about here?
What is that lever?
Oh, right.
Okay.
Keep it open, please.
And this leads where?
Right.
What is that lever over there?
Oh, okay.
Um.
I'm so lost.
Ah, okay.
Nice shortcut there.
I like that.
Okay.
What about this way?
What's up here?
Oh, this is below the theater, right?
Yeah, this should lead up to the theater.
Yes.
Everyone is gone now.
Where did everyone go?
And where is this door I found down here?
I cannot find it.
I wish I had a map or something.
Because I am omega lost.
So let's try going back where we came from here.
So now we can try to do...
Path to theater from there.
Where does that lead?
Okay, there it is.
No, I need something.
I need this shape.
Whatever that is.
Okay, so let's remember this.
To get to this door, we have to follow the path towards the theater.
Oh, also, by the way, look at this.
That's the shape of the zoom terminal.
Isn't it?
This has to mean that...
Oh, is it because I didn't do all the zoom terminals in this level?
That's probably what that means.
Let's go to the zoom terminal.
Yeah, back this way.
Click on that.
Here.
But no, there's no circle in this one.
I thought maybe we needed to do both of these to unlock the door or something.
Hmm.
Well, shit.
Okay, let's get back up, I guess, and keep exploring for now.
Yeah, that was kind of a detour, huh?
At least I figured out some of the stuff with the zoom terminals.
I'm gonna take a quick break and continue in the next.
I'll see you.
Bye-bye.